Guide to the Wesley C. Salmon Papers, 1950-2003 ASP.2003.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1960-2010; 1963-2001; I.
  - Correspondents - S-T, 15.
    - Stein, Betty, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Stein, Michael, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Sterrett, Susan, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Steve, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Stevens, Charles, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Stewart, Bob, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Stewart, Douglas, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Stewart, John, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Stimpson, Cathenne, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Stine, William, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Stipich, N, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Storrs, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Stout, A.K., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Straker, Stephen, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Straker, Stephen, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Storm, Erik, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Stove, David, 1975-1985 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Strauss, Martin, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Strawson, Galen, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Stricker, Edward, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Striker, Gisela, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Strong, Lyndall, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Stroyls, John, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Struckman, Robert, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Stuart, Gaby, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Sturgeon, Robert, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Sturrock, P.A., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - Suchting, W.A., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Sukiennik, Adelaide, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Suppe, Fredrick, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Supples, Patrick, 1964-1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Susanna, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Sutherland, John, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Suttle, Bruce, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Sutton, Ceatta, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Suzuki, MacGregor, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Svetlik, John, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Swain, Marshall, 1968-1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Swartz, Robert, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Swartz, Norman, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Swift, Carol, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Swinburne, Richard, 1969-1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Swoyer, Chris, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Sylvain, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - "Synthese", 1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Sypherd, Paul, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Szabo, Laszlo, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Szekely, D.L., 1968-1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Szubka, Tadeusz, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Tadeusiak, Julia, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Tait, Bill, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Tamburino, John, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Tamthai, Mark, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Tang, Paul, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Taylor, Charles, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Taylor, G.G., undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Taylor, G.M., 1987 (Box 18, Folder 29 b)
    - Taylor, Richard, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Telfer, M.A., 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Teller, Paul, 1967-1994 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Tennant, Neil, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Thatcher, Sanford, 1970-1988 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Therien, Norwell, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Thoma, Klaus, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Thomas, Robert, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Thomason, James, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Thomason, Rich, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Thompson, Glenn, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Thompson, Nancy, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Thomsett, Derek, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Thomson, James, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Thorsheim, H.I., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Tiwari, Siva, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Trans World Airlines, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Tomas, Vincent, 1966-1978 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Tooley, Michael, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Toraldo di Francia, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Toretti, Roberto, 1971-1985 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Towe, Joe, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Townsend, Bruce, 1972-1980 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Trahan, Jeffrey, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Trapp, Rainer, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Treadwell, Louis, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Tribus, Myron, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Trivelpiece, Alvin, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Trudgen, Richard, (Dickenson Publishing), 1973-1977 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Trusted, Jennifer, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Tucker, John, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Turbott, G.G., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Turnbull, Robert, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Turner, Dean, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Turner, Frank, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Turner, Stephen, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Twiggs, James, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Correspondents -U-V, 16.
    - Uchii, Sochichi, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Underhill, Lee, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Underwood, Tane, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Ungever, Dave, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - University of California, L.A., 1977-1996 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - University of California Press, 1966-1992 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1968-1996 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - University College, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - University of Lagos, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - University of Minnesota Press, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - University of Pittsburgh Press, 1967-1997 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Uyeyama, Teru, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Vakili, Cyrus, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Van Brakel, J, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Van Cleve, James, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Van Fraassen, Bas, 1966-1986 (Box 18, Folder 82-83)
    - Van de Kamp, Carla, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Van der Merwe, Alwyn, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Van Erra, James, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Van Haist, Jane, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Van Straaten, Zak, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Vana, Clara, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Vance, B.E., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Vasconez, Marcelo, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Vasko, Michael, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Vayda, Andrew, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Vendler, Zeno, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Vielis, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Vilnay, Oren, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Vineein, Nicholas, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Vinvent, Roy, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Vitek, William, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Viton, Philip, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Vlastos, Gregory, 1965-1972 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Von Bretzel, Phillip, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Von Wright, G.H., 1963-1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondents - W, 17.
    - W.H. Freeman & Co., 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Wadia, Pheroze, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Wald, Ann, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Wald, Paula, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Walker, A.G., 1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Wallace, James, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Wallace, John, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Wallace, William, 1972-1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Waller, Harold, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Waller, William, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Walsh, June, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Walters, Robert, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Warder, Michael, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Ware, Richard, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Warnow, Joan, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Warren, Ariene, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Wartofsky, Maux, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Wasserstrom, Richard, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Waterman, Scott, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Waters, Lindsay, 1980-1985 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Watkins, Ginny, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Watkins, John "JWN", 1966-1988 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Watson, Richard, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Wayne, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Weatherhead, Kingsley, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Weaver, A.B., 1975 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Webb, John, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Webb, Peter, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Webber, Jean, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Webster, Ron, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Weil, Robert, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Weil, Vivian, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Weinberg, Steven, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Weiner, Charles, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Weingartner, Paul, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Weingartner, Rudolph, 1968-1989 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Weinstein, Don, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Weis, Albrecht, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Weisman, Joseph, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Welch, Claude, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Wells, Donald, 1969-1978 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Werkmeister, W.H., 1963-1973 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Werntz, James, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Wessels, Linda, 1972-1990 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Westfall, Richard "Sam", 1966-1975 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Westheimer, Frank, 1975-1988 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Wettersten, John, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Wehstein, Howard, 1982-1992 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Weyant, R.G., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Whitbeck, Caroline, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - White, Jan, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - White, Michael, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - White, Patricia, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Whitesel, R.G., 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Whiting, Jennifer, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Whitmer, Jeffrey, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Wiener, Phillip, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Wienpahl, Paul, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Wiley and Sons Publishing, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Williams, Donald, 1963-1975 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Williams, Eric, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Williams, Peter, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Williams, Warwick, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Williamson, Thomas, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Wilson, Arnold, 1979-1990 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Wine, Eugene, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Winnie, John, 1972-1994 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Winsatt, Bill, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Wojcick, Ryszard, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Wolenski, Jan, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Wolfson, Maltin, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Wolke, Robert, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Woiters, Gereon, 1987-1994 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Wood, Allen, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Wood, James, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Woodcock, William, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Woodruff, Paul, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Woods, John, 1975-1986 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Woodward, James, 1982-1994 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Warrel, John, 1974-1994 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Wright, Larry, 1969-1979 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Wright, Marshall, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Wu-Lun, Jin, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Wu, Wayne, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - Wunsch, G, undated (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - Wustenhube, Axel, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Correspondents - X-Z, Misc., 18.
    - Xiao-Wu, Li, 1986-1997 (Box 19 b, Folder 1)
    - Yamamoto, Yutaka, 1975 (Box 19 b, Folder 2)
    - Ye, Lang, 1997 (Box 19 b, Folder 3)
    - Yolton, John, 1965-1966 (Box 19 b, Folder 4)
    - Yonker, Justin, 1998 (Box 19 b, Folder 5)
    - Yost, Robert, 1965-1978 (Box 19 b, Folder 6)
    - Young, Dick, 1970 (Box 19 b, Folder 7)
    - Youngman, David, 1969 (Box 19 b, Folder 8)
    - Yourgrau, Wolfgang, 1966-1977 (Box 19 b, Folder 9)
    - Yutaka, 1973 (Box 19 b, Folder 10)
    - Zabell, Sandy, 1985 (Box 19 b, Folder 11)
    - Zachary, Robert, 1969-1976 (Box 19 b, Folder 12)
    - Zaner, Richard, 1975 (Box 19 b, Folder 13)
    - Zanardo, Alberto, 1994 (Box 19 b, Folder 14)
    - Zhou, Beihai, 1997 (Box 19 b, Folder 15)
    - Zielonacka-Lis, Eaw, 1992 (Box 19 b, Folder 16)
    - Zimmer, Paul, (University of Pittsburgh), 1973 (Box 19 b, Folder 17)
    - Zimmerman, Dean, 1998 (Box 19 b, Folder 18)
    - Zoeteman, H.E., 1983 (Box 19 b, Folder 19)
    - Zorzato, Paolo, 1985-1986 (Box 19 b, Folder 20)
    - Zuck, Linda, 1980 (Box 19 b, Folder 21)
    - Zuesse, Eric, 1986 (Box 19 b, Folder 22)
    - Zwirm, Larry, 1975-1976 (Box 19 b, Folder 23)
    - Zytkow, Jan, 1979 (Box 19 b, Folder 24)
    - Misc., Various (Box 19 b, Folder 25)
  - Recommendation Letters, A-Z [Restricted], 1963-1997
    Conditions Governing Access
    Recommendation Letters, Restricted
- Manuscripts, 1957-2001; 1960-2001; II.
  This series contains handwritten notes, handwritten drafts, annotated early manuscripts, and finished copies of the books that Salmon wrote, as well as parallel materials for his professional articles. The series has been divided into three subseries: material dealing with Salmon's books, material dealing with his professional articles in philosophy, and articles written by others but dedicated to Salmon.
  - Monograph Manuscripts, 1965-2001; 1.
    This subseries contains all working materials for books that Salmon published as well those that were not published. There will be early drafts, working manuscripts, and support materials for these books. The documents are gathered by book and sub-divided by chapters or divisions of the books.
    - Causality and Explanation: Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Causality and Explanation: Permissions, 1991-1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Causality and Explanation: Draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Causality and Explanation: Draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Causality and Explanation: Draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Causality and Explanation: Draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Causality and Explanation: Draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Causality and Explanation: Draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Contemporary Perspectives in Philosophy: Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Contemporary Perspectives in Philosophy: Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Contemporary Perspectives in Philosophy: Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Contemporary Perspectives in Philosophy: Sales Figures, 1964-1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Perspectives in Philosophy: Sales Figures, 1964-1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Doing Logic: Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Doing Logic: Draft, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Doing Logic: Draft, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Doing Logic: Draft, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Doing Logic: Draft, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Foundations of Scientific Inference, 1953-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Foundations of Scientific Inference, 1953-1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Four Decades: Correspondence and Reviews, 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Four Decades: Research Assistant Work, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Four Decades: Notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Four Decades: Italian Translation Correspondence, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Four Decades: Fetzer's Reply, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
    - Hans Reichenbach: Logical Empiricist, 1975-1989 (Box 24, Folder 1-6)
    - Induction, Confirmation, and Probability: Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Induction, Confirmation, and Probability: Manuscript, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Induction, Confirmation, and Probability: Manuscript, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Induction, Confirmation, and Probability: Manuscript, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Introduction to the Philosophy of Science: Correspondence, 1989-1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Introduction to the Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Introduction to the Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 25, Folder 6 B)
    - Italian Science and Letters: Draft, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Italian Science and Letters: Draft, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Italian Science and Letters: Draft, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Italian Science and Letters: Draft, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Limitations of Deductivism, 1980-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Limitations of Deductivism, 1980-1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Logic: 1st Edition, 1961-1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Logic: 1st Edition, 1961-1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Logic: 2nd Edition, 1972-1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Logic: 2nd Edition, 1972-1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Logic: 3rd Edition, 1982-1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Logic: 3rd Edition, 1982-1989 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Logic: 3rd Edition, 1982-1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Logic: Supplement, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Logic: Notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Logic: Drafts, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Logic: Drafts, undated (Box 27, Folder 12 B)
    - Logic, Language, and the Structure of Scientific Theories, 1991-2003 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Logic, Language, and the Structure of Scientific Theories, 1991-2003 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Logic, Language, and the Structure of Scientific Theories, 1991-2003 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Logic, Language, and the Structure of Scientific Theories: Index, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Logical Empiricism: History and Contemporary Perspectives, 2000-2004 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Logical Empiricism: History and Contemporary Perspectives, 2000-2004 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Philosophical Problem of Probability, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Philosophical Problem of Probability, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Philosophy of Science: Figures and Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Philosophy of Science: Draft, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Popular Lectures: Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Scientific Explanation: Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Scientific Explanation: Draft and Reviews, 1989-1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Scientific Explanation and the Causal Structure of the World: Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 32, Folder 3-5)
    - Scientific Explanation and the Causal Structure of the World: Notes, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Scientific Explanation and the Causal Structure of the World: Reviews, 1984-1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Space, Time, and Motion: 1st Edition, 1970-1978 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
    - Space, Time, and Motion: 2nd Edition, 1978-1995 (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
    - Space, Time, and Motion: Copyright and Royalties, 1975-1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Statistical Explanation and Statistical Relevance: Correspondence, 1970-1991 (Box 33, Folder 8-9)
    - Statistical Explanation and Statistical Relevance: Draft and Reviews, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified Manuscript: Draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Manuscript: Draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Manuscript: Draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified Manuscript: Draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Manuscript: Draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified Manuscript: Draft, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Zeno's Paradoxes: Correspondence, 1966-2001 (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
    - Zeno's Paradoxes: Permissions, 1963-1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Zeno's Paradoxes: Corrections, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Zeno's Paradoxes: Promotional Material, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Zeno's Paradoxes: Royalties, 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Zeno's Paradoxes: 2nd Edition, 1983-2000 (Box 35, Folder 10-14)
  - Article Manuscripts, 1965-2001; 2.
    This subseries contains working materials for Salmon's professional articles in philosophy. There are handwritten materials, early typescripts, drafts, and annotated later drafts.
    - "Alternative Models of Scientific Explanation- correspondence", 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - "Analytic Probabilities vs. David Hume", 1953-1990 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - "Ancient Geometry and Modern Epistemology", 1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - "Appraisal of Theories: Kuhn Meets Bayes", 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - "Arguments on Atomism", undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - "An 'AT-AT' Theory of Causal Influence", 1977 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - "Axiomatization of the Theory of Relativity: Forward", 1969 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - "Barker's Theory of the Absolute", 1959 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - "Bayes Theorem and Experimental Controls - correspondence", 1972 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - "Bayes's Theorem and the History of Science", 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Cambridge Dictionary of Philosophy, 1990-1995 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - "Carnap", 1992-1999 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - "Carnap, Hempel, and Reichenbach on Scientific Realism", undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - "Carnap's Inductive Logic", 1967-1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - "Causal Propensities", 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - "La Causalita", 1993 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - "Causality and Explanation: A Reply to Two Critiques", 1996 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - "Causality in Archaeological Explanation", 1981 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - "Causality in Quantum Mechanics", undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - "Causality: Production and Propagation", 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - "Causality Without Counterfactuals", 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - "Causation", 1999 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - "Changing One's Convictions", 1991 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - "Clocks and Simultaneity", 1973-1976 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - "Clocks and Simultaneity, Introduction", 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - "Comets, Pollen, and Dreams", 1982 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - "Comments on Barker's 'Role of Simplicity in Explanation'", 1961 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - "Comments on Bas Van Fraaseen's 'Probability and Individuation'", 1969 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - "Comments on Butts, Parrini, Galavotti, and Festa", 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - "Comments on Butts, Parrini, Galavotti, and Festa", 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - "Comment: Carnap on Realism", undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - "Comment on Coffa", 1974 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - "Comment on Glymour's 'Theory and Evidence','', undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - "Comment on R.M. Martin", 1969 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - "Comment on Quickie Q503", 1971 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - "Comment on Schlesinger and Grunbaum", 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - "Commit It Then to The Flames", 2001 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Companion to Epistemology, 1990-1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Companion to Metaphysics, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - "La Comprension Cientifica En El Siglo Viente", 1994 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - "Concept on Inductive Evidence", 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - "Confirmation", undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - "Confirmation: Scientific American", 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - "Confirmation: Scientific American", 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - "Confirmation and Relevance", 1972-1975 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - "Conflicting Conception of Scientific Explanation", 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - "Consistency and Non Contradiction", undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - "Consistency, Transitivity, and Inductive Support", 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - "Correspondence Rules", 1969 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - "Conventionality of Simultaneity", 1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - "Cronica", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - "Curvature of Space", 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - "Deductive and Inductive Explanation", 1964 (Box 38, Folder 8)